{"test_questions": [[{"question": "ENORMOUS", "opta": "Soft", "optb": "Average", "optc": "Tiny", "optd": "Weak", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "COMMISSIONED", "opta": "Started", "optb": "Closed", "optc": "Finished", "optd": "Terminated", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "ARTIFICIAL", "opta": "Red", "optb": "Natural", "optc": "Truthful", "optd": "Solid", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "EXODUS", "opta": "Influx", "optb": "Home-coming", "optc": "Return", "optd": "Restoration", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "RELINQUISH", "opta": "Abdicate", "optb": "Renounce", "optc": "Possess", "optd": "Deny", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "EXPAND", "opta": "Convert", "optb": "Condense", "optc": "Congest", "optd": "Conclude", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "MORTAL", "opta": "Divine", "optb": "Immortal", "optc": "Spiritual", "optd": "Eternal", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "QUIESCENT", "opta": "ACTIVE", "optb": "Dormant", "optc": "Weak", "optd": "Unconcerned", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "OBEYING", "opta": "Ordering", "optb": "Following", "optc": "Refusing", "optd": "Contradicting", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "FRAUDULENT", "opta": "Candid", "optb": "Direct", "optc": "Forthright", "optd": "Genuine", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "FLAGITIOUS", "opta": "Innocent", "optb": "Vapid", "optc": "Ignorant", "optd": "Frivolous", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "BELITTLE", "opta": "Criticize", "optb": "Flatter", "optc": "Exaggerate", "optd": "Adore", "ans": "C", "explanation": "Main Entry: belittle\nPart of Speech: verb\nDefinition: detract\nSynonyms: bad-mouth, blister, criticize, cut down to size, cut to the quick, decry, deprecate, depreciate, deride, derogate, diminish, discount, discredit, disparage, dispraise, downgrade, downplay, dump on, knock*, lower, minimize, pan, pooh pooh, poor mouth, put down, rip*, roast, run down, scoff at, scorch*, scorn, shoot down, shoot full of holes, slam*, smear, sneer at, sour grapes, squash, squelch, take a swipe at, take down, take down a peg, tear down, underestimate, underrate, undervalue, write off.\nAntonyms: build up, exaggerate, praise, value"}, {"question": "STARTLED", "opta": "Amused", "optb": "Relaxed", "optc": "Endless", "optd": "Astonished", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "BUSY", "opta": "Occupied", "optb": "Engrossed", "optc": "Relaxed", "optd": "Engaged", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "FRESH", "opta": "Faulty", "optb": "Sluggish", "optc": "Disgraceful", "optd": "Stale", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "CULPABLE", "opta": "Defendable", "optb": "Blameless", "optc": "Careless", "optd": "Irresponsible", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "EVASIVE", "opta": "Free", "optb": "Honest", "optc": "Liberal", "optd": "Frank", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "GREGARIOUS", "opta": "Antisocial", "optb": "Glorious", "optc": "Horrendous", "optd": "Similar", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "AWARE", "opta": "Uncertain", "optb": "Ignorant", "optc": "Sure", "optd": "Doubtful", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "HIRSUTE", "opta": "Scaly", "optb": "Bald", "optc": "Erudite", "optd": "Quiet", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "SHRINK", "opta": "Contract", "optb": "Spoil", "optc": "Expand", "optd": "Stretch", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "COMMON", "opta": "Rare", "optb": "Small", "optc": "Petty", "optd": "Poor", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "COMFORT", "opta": "Uncomfort", "optb": "Miscomfort", "optc": "Discomfort", "optd": "None Of These", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "DEAR", "opta": "Priceless", "optb": "Free", "optc": "Worthless", "optd": "Cheap", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "ARROGANT", "opta": "Humble", "optb": "Cowardly", "optc": "Egotistic", "optd": "Gentlemanly", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "VICTORIOUS", "opta": "Defeated", "optb": "Annexed", "optc": "Destroyed", "optd": "Vanquished", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "GRACEFUL", "opta": "Rough", "optb": "Expert", "optc": "Miserable", "optd": "Awkward", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "NADIR", "opta": "Modernity", "optb": "Zenith", "optc": "Liberty", "optd": "Progress", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "EXTRAVAGANCE", "opta": "Luxury", "optb": "Poverty", "optc": "Economical", "optd": "Cheapness", "ans": "C", "explanation": "Main Entry: extravagant\n\nPart of Speech: adjective\n\nDefinition: indulgent, wasteful\n\nSynonyms: absurd, bizarre, costly, crazy, exaggerated, excessive, exorbitant, expensive, extortionate, extreme, fanciful, fancy, fantastic, flamboyant, flashy, foolish, garish, gaudy, grandiose, immoderate, implausible, improvident, imprudent, inordinate, lavish, ludicrous, nonsensical, ornate, ostentatious, outrageous, overpriced, preposterous, pretentious, prodigal, profligate, reckless, ridiculous, showy, silly, spendthrift, steep, unbalanced, unconscionable, unreasonable, unrestrained\n\nAntonyms: close, economical, moderate, provident, reasonable, saving, stingy, thrifty, unpretentious"}, {"question": "PERTINENT", "opta": "Irrational", "optb": "Irregular", "optc": "Insistent", "optd": "Irrelevant", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "OBSCURE", "opta": "Implicit", "optb": "Obnoxious", "optc": "Explicit", "optd": "Pedantic", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "URBANE", "opta": "Illiterate", "optb": "Backward", "optc": "Discourteous", "optd": "Orthodox", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "VANITY", "opta": "Pride", "optb": "Humility", "optc": "Conceit", "optd": "Ostentatious", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "RARELY", "opta": "Hardly", "optb": "Definately", "optc": "Frequently", "optd": "Periodically", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "MALICIOUS", "opta": "Kind", "optb": "Boastful", "optc": "Generous", "optd": "Indifferent", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "EPILOGUE", "opta": "Dialogue", "optb": "Prelude", "optc": "Post script", "optd": "Epigram", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "CAPACIOUS", "opta": "Limited", "optb": "Caring", "optc": "Foolish", "optd": "Changeable", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "CONDENSE", "opta": "Expand", "optb": "Distribute", "optc": "Interpret", "optd": "Lengthen", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "ADAPTABLE", "opta": "Adoptable", "optb": "Flexible", "optc": "Yielding", "optd": "Rigid", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "SACROSANCT", "opta": "Irreligious", "optb": "Unethical", "optc": "Irreverent", "optd": "Unholy", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "INDISCREET", "opta": "Reliable", "optb": "Honest", "optc": "Prudent", "optd": "Stupid", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "FAMILIAR", "opta": "Unpleasant", "optb": "Dangerous", "optc": "Friendly", "optd": "Strange", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "TANGIBLE", "opta": "Ethereal", "optb": "Concrete", "optc": "Actual", "optd": "Solid", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "LOVE", "opta": "Villainy", "optb": "Hatred", "optc": "Compulsion", "optd": "Force", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "FAMOUS", "opta": "Disgraced", "optb": "Unknown", "optc": "Evil", "optd": "Popular", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "ABSOLUTE", "opta": "Deficient", "optb": "Faulty", "optc": "Limited", "optd": "Scarce", "ans": "C", "explanation": "Word: absolute \n\nPart of Speech: adjective \n\nDefinition: without limit \n\nSynonyms: complete, consummate, downright, entire, flat out, free, full, infinite, no catch, no fine print, no holds barred, no ifs ands or buts, no joke, no strings attached, outright, plenary, pure, sheer, simple, straight out, supreme, thorough, total, unabridged, unadulterated, unconditional, unlimited, unqualified, unrestricted, utter \n\nAntonyms: accountable, circumscribed, limited, restricted, tractable"}, {"question": "FRUGAL", "opta": "Copious", "optb": "Extravagant", "optc": "Generous", "optd": "Ostentatious", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "INSIPID", "opta": "Tasty", "optb": "Stupid", "optc": "Discreet", "optd": "Feast", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "ABLE", "opta": "Disable", "optb": "Inable", "optc": "Unable", "optd": "Misable", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "HOSTILITY", "opta": "Courtesy", "optb": "Hospitality", "optc": "Relationship", "optd": "Friendliness", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "CROWDED", "opta": "Busy", "optb": "Congested", "optc": "Quiet", "optd": "Deserted", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "COMIC", "opta": "Emotional", "optb": "Tragic", "optc": "Fearful", "optd": "Painful", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "HAPLESS", "opta": "Cheerful", "optb": "Consistent", "optc": "Fortunate", "optd": "Shapely", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "FLIMSY", "opta": "Frail", "optb": "Filthy", "optc": "Firm", "optd": "Flippant", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "EQUANIMITY", "opta": "Resentment", "optb": "Dubiousness", "optc": "Duplicity", "optd": "Excitement", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "ADDITION", "opta": "Division", "optb": "Enumeration", "optc": "Subtraction", "optd": "Multiplication", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "ZENITH", "opta": "Acme", "optb": "Top", "optc": "Nadir", "optd": "Pinnacle", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "DOUBTFUL", "opta": "Famous", "optb": "Certain", "optc": "Fixed", "optd": "Important", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "PERENNIAL", "opta": "Frequent", "optb": "Regular", "optc": "Lasting", "optd": "Rare", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "BENIGN", "opta": "Malevolent", "optb": "Soft", "optc": "Friendly", "optd": "Unwise", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "HINDRANCE", "opta": "Aid", "optb": "Persuasion", "optc": "Cooperation", "optd": "Agreement", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "EXTRICATE", "opta": "Manifest", "optb": "Palpable", "optc": "Release", "optd": "Entangle", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "REPRESS", "opta": "Inhibit", "optb": "Liberate", "optc": "Curb", "optd": "Quell", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "ACQUITTED", "opta": "Freed", "optb": "Burdened", "optc": "Convicted", "optd": "Entrusted", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "PROVOCATION", "opta": "Vocation", "optb": "Pacification", "optc": "Peace", "optd": "Destruction", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "SUBSERVIENT", "opta": "Aggressive", "optb": "Straightforward", "optc": "Dignified", "optd": "Supercilious", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "LEND", "opta": "Borrow", "optb": "Cheat", "optc": "Pawn", "optd": "Hire", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "FAINT-HEARTED", "opta": "Warm-hearted", "optb": "Full-blooded", "optc": "Hot-blooded", "optd": "Stout-hearted", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "REMISS", "opta": "Forgetful", "optb": "Watchful", "optc": "Dutiful", "optd": "Harmful", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "TRANSPARENT", "opta": "Semi-transparent", "optb": "Muddy", "optc": "Opaque", "optd": "Dark", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "HONORARY", "opta": "Dishonorable", "optb": "Reputed", "optc": "Paid", "optd": "Official", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "METICULOUS", "opta": "Mutual", "optb": "Shaggy", "optc": "Meretricious", "optd": "Slovenly", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "LOQUACIOUS", "opta": "Reticent", "optb": "Talkative", "optc": "Garrulous", "optd": "Verbose", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "CONFESS", "opta": "Deny", "optb": "Refuse", "optc": "Contest", "optd": "Contend", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "ANNOY", "opta": "Praise", "optb": "Rejoice", "optc": "Please", "optd": "Reward", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "REPEL", "opta": "Attend", "optb": "Concentrate", "optc": "Continue", "optd": "Attract", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "SUPPRESS", "opta": "Encourage", "optb": "Allow", "optc": "Praise", "optd": "Permit", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "NIGGARDLY", "opta": "Frugal", "optb": "Thrifty", "optc": "Stingy", "optd": "Generous", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "IMPASSE", "opta": "Resurgence", "optb": "Breakthrough", "optc": "Continuation", "optd": "Combination", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "HAPHAZARD", "opta": "Fortuitous", "optb": "Indifferent", "optc": "Deliberate", "optd": "Accidental", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "DENSITY", "opta": "Rarity", "optb": "Intelligence", "optc": "Clarity", "optd": "Brightness", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "ADHERENT", "opta": "Detractor", "optb": "Enemy", "optc": "Alien", "optd": "Rival", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "BASE", "opta": "Climax", "optb": "Height", "optc": "Top", "optd": "Roof", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "PATCHY", "opta": "Attractive", "optb": "Uniform", "optc": "Simple", "optd": "Clear", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "ENMITY", "opta": "Important", "optb": "Unnecessary", "optc": "Friendship", "optd": "Likeness", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "HOLLOW", "opta": "Filled", "optb": "Solid", "optc": "Strong", "optd": "Substantial", "ans": "B", "explanation": "Main Entry: hollow \nPart of Speech: adjective\nDefinition: empty, hollowed out\nSynonyms: alveolate, arched, carved out, cavernous, cleft, concave, cup-shaped, cupped, curved, deep-set, depressed, dimpled, excavated, incurved, indented, infundibular, not solid, notched, pitted, striated, sunken, troughlike, unfilled, vacant, vaulted, void\nAntonyms: convex, full, raised, solid."}, {"question": "VALUABLE", "opta": "Invaluable", "optb": "Worthless", "optc": "Inferior", "optd": "Lowly", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "GULLIBLE", "opta": "Incredulous", "optb": "Fickle", "optc": "Easy", "optd": "Stylish", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "INDUSTRIOUS", "opta": "Indifferent", "optb": "Indolent", "optc": "Casual", "optd": "Passive", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "AUTONOMY", "opta": "Slavery", "optb": "Subordination", "optc": "Dependence", "optd": "Submissiveness", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "ALIEN", "opta": "Native", "optb": "Domiciled", "optc": "Natural", "optd": "Resident", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "SYNTHETIC", "opta": "Affable", "optb": "Natural", "optc": "Plastic", "optd": "Cosmetic", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "BALANCE", "opta": "Disbalance", "optb": "Misbalance", "optc": "Debalance", "optd": "Imbalance", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "LIABILITY", "opta": "Property", "optb": "Assets", "optc": "Debt", "optd": "Treasure", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "MOUNTAIN", "opta": "Plain", "optb": "Plateau", "optc": "Precipice", "optd": "Valley", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "STATIONARY", "opta": "Active", "optb": "Mobile", "optc": "Rapid", "optd": "Busy", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "CONCEDE", "opta": "Object", "optb": "Refuse", "optc": "Grant", "optd": "Accede", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "VIOLENT", "opta": "Humble", "optb": "Harmless", "optc": "Gentle", "optd": "Tame", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "VIRTUOUS", "opta": "Wicked", "optb": "Corrupt", "optc": "Vicious", "optd": "Scandalous", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "GAIN", "opta": "Loose", "optb": "Fall", "optc": "Lost", "optd": "Lose", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "PRELIMINARY", "opta": "Final", "optb": "First", "optc": "Secondary", "optd": "Initial", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "DEFIANCE", "opta": "Anxiety", "optb": "Obedience", "optc": "Suspicion", "optd": "Dismay", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "ENCOURAGE", "opta": "Dampen", "optb": "Disapprove", "optc": "Discourage", "optd": "Warn", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "LUCID", "opta": "Glory", "optb": "Noisy", "optc": "Obscure", "optd": "Distinct", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "STRINGENT", "opta": "General", "optb": "Vehement", "optc": "Lenient", "optd": "Magnanimous", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "MINOR", "opta": "Big", "optb": "Major", "optc": "Tall", "optd": "Heavy", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "REVEALED", "opta": "Denied", "optb": "Concealed", "optc": "Ignored", "optd": "Overlooked", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "ESSENTIAL", "opta": "Extra", "optb": "Noughts", "optc": "Minors", "optd": "Trivial", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "HYPOCRITICAL", "opta": "Gentle", "optb": "Sincere", "optc": "Amiable", "optd": "Dependable", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "FICKLE", "opta": "Courageous", "optb": "Sincere", "optc": "Steadfast", "optd": "Humble", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}